Wrong time. Wrong place. Wrong number.
Lucky Number Slevin is a drama, thriller, crime film directed by Paul McGuigan.
Slevin is mistakenly put in the middle of a personal war
between the city’s biggest criminal bosses.
Under constant watch, Slevin must try not to get killed by an infamous assassin
and come up with an idea of how to get out of his current dilemma.
Slevin, played by Josh Hartnett.
The Boss, played by Morgan Freeman.
The Rabbi, played by Ben Kingsley.
Lindsey, played by Lucy Liu.
Mr. Goodkat, played by Bruce Willis.
Det. Brikowski, played by Stanley Tucci.
Lucky Number Slevin (also known as The Wrong Man in Australia) is a 2006 black comedy neo-noir
crime thriller film directed by Paul McGuigan and written by Jason Smilovic.
The film stars Josh Hartnett, Lucy Liu, Bruce Willis,
Stanley Tucci, Ben Kingsley, and Morgan Freeman.
Lucky Number Slevin was released in the United Kingdom on April 7, 2006, by Entertainment Film
Distributors, and in the United States on February 24, 2006, by MGM Distribution Co.
The film explores themes of sniper, assassin,
assassination, gambling debt, identity.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.